productwiki.com 2010-01-05

# Privacy Policy - ProductWiki unbiased product reviews

This privacy policy describes how we collect and use personal data provided by our users. If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at contact@productwiki.com or send us a note to:

ProductWiki Inc  
Attn: Privacy Officer  
11 - 295 Hagey Blvd.  
Waterloo, ON N2L 6R5

## What is Collected and How the Data is Used

### Member Account Data

A member account is required to contribute to the site in almost all ways, except for voting on a review's helpfulness. When you sign up for a member account, you are need to provide:

  * name and password - we use this information to create and manage your user account;

  * email address - we will use this address for site communications, this includes, but not limited to, site news, member messages. If you opt out of e-mails we won't send you any, ever;

If you are logged in when you post content on the site, the content will be identified under your name.

We do not store your actual password, instead we store a one-way hash that is generated using our own private key and your supplied password, this way nobody, even the admins at ProductWiki can know your password.

Contributions to the site are assumed to be permanent and may exist on ProductWiki servers, or data archives, whether visible to the public or not. If content is deleted from ProductWiki website properties that does not guarantee the content is not housed in automated backups or disk cache which is accessible to high-level server admins.

### Community Features

**Profiles**

Once you have an account, you may enhance it by providing information under the "About Me" section, or uploading a picture to be used as your avatar. This information will be disclosed publicly on the site under your profile. You are not required to provide this information. We offer users the opportunity to provide this profile information in order to enhance the richness of our online community. We may use the information you provide us in your profile to customize your experience by showing you content relevant to your areas of interest.

**Your Contributions**

It goes without saying that any personally identifiable information that you submit on any review, discussion thread or elsewhere on the site can be read, collected, or used by other user of the site and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit to the website.

**Private Messaging**

If you want to contact another ProductWiki registered member, you may send a private message (PM) through the site. You will be identified to that user only by your user name, and we will not disclose your email address to that member or theirs to you.

### Cookies, Web Beacons and Web Logs

We set a temporary session cookie whenever you visit the site. It will be deleted when you close your browser. If you merely read the site without logging in, you may instruct your browser to deny this cookie.

When you log into the site, we may set a persistent cookie, which will allow us to recognize you as an existing registered member and avoid the need to log into the site again. These cookies may last for up to 365 days. You may clear these cookies in your browser after a session in which you have logged in.

Our web pages may also contain an electronic file called a web beacon that allows us to count users who have visited that page or to access certain cookies.

Our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. We store this data in files called web logs. These web logs may include information such as your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the site you came from, the next site you visit and cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

None of the data collected through web beacons, cookies or web log data provides us with any personal information about you. We use this data on an aggregated basis to analyze how our users are interacting with the site and to customize your experience, such as by remembering your preferences and showing you content that you have tagged. If you are logged in to the site, we could associate information about your site usage that is collected by cookies, web beacons and web logs with your user account. However, we don't do this on an individual basis other than in cases of suspected abuse or illegal behavior. See our policy below about Investigating Abuse.

**Advertisers' Cookies**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our site. When you view ads on our site, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed on your browser by the ad-serving company. In addition, the ad-serving companies may use web beacons to help manage and optimize our online advertising. The information collected by the ad-serving companies may be used to target ads to you on this site, on other sites that you visit, and other forms of media. To "opt-out" of these ad-serving cookies and web beacons, [please click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Information for Contests and Sweepstakes**

If we offer a contest or sweepstakes, we may ask for additional information such as name, address, and phone number in order to provide the winner with their prize. We would not use that information for any other purpose unless we receive consent at the time you provide the information.

## Special Rules for Children

f you are under 18, we also ask that you not include any personal information in your profile (such as your name, city or date of birth) or in your posts on the site.

## Information Sharing.

**Third Parties**

We will never provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties without your consent, except as described under "Our Service Provider" and "Investigating Abuse". We may provide third parties with aggregated or anonymous data about our users and their usage of our services that do not contain any individual's personally identifiable information.

**Our Service Providers**

We may hire third-parties to help us provide our services to you. These services may include technical services, customer support, email message deployment, data processing and other services. It may be necessary for us to provide these third parties with some of you personal information in order for them to fulfill their services. For example, we use a third party to send our e-mail newsletters, so if you sign up for a newsletter, we will provide them your email address and your first and last name as necessary to provide you with the newsletter. These third parties do no retain, share or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information to providing services to us.

## Links to Other Sites

This web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us, including links in advertisements. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site to which you provide information.

## Investigating Potential Abuse

We may use any information provided to us by a user, including personally identifiable information, along with any data gathered from our web logs and from third parties to conduct investigations, and we may disclose this information to third parties, including law enforcement officials, investigators, or private parties seeking to protect and enforce their rights; if

  * we have a good faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, judicial proceeding, legal process, subpoena or warrant;

  * we have a good faith belief that it is necessary to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; or

  * we believe that your actions violate the law or our Terms of Use or threaten the rights, property, or safety of our company, our users, or others.

## Business Transfer

If we sell all or a portion of our business, we may transfer some or all of your information as a part of the sale.

## Accessing and Changing Your Account Information.

You can review your personal information and make any desired changes at any time by logging in to your account and editing the information on your profile page. If you want to close your ProductWiki account, send an email to contact@productwiki.com using the email account that you used to create your account. Within ten business days we will remove your profile and other personally identifiable information from our publicly viewable data, but your posts (with user name) will remain. We may retain certain data contributed by you if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained data will continue to be subject to the terms of our Privacy Policy.

## Security

In order to secure your personal information, access to your user account from the website is password-protected. While we take security very seriously, no data transmission over the Internet or information storage technology is 100% secure. If you suspect that your ProductWiki account has been compromised, please email us at contact@productwiki.com.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

If we make a material change in the way we use the personal data of our users, we will modify our privacy policy and will describe the changes under "Changes to the Privacy Policy". Your use of the website after any published change signifies your consent to the application of the revised policy to all information contributed before or after the date of those changes.
